<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Three | Automate Fixes &amp; Runtime Scanning on Cloud DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/30_module_three.html</link><description>Recent content in Three | Automate Fixes &amp; Runtime Scanning on Cloud DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/30_module_three/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automate Fixes through Pull Requests</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/30_module_three/3002_bridgecrew_automate_pr_remediation.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/30_module_three/3002_bridgecrew_automate_pr_remediation.html</guid><description>Automate Fixes Through Pull Requests By adding another Intgration into Bridgecrew, we can generate automated Pull Requests (PR&amp;rsquo;s) into your Github repository, to update your CloudFormation manifests and fix security issues!
To do this, we&amp;rsquo;ll use the &amp;ldquo;Github&amp;rdquo; Source Control integration within the Bridgecrew Dashboard, allowing Bridgecrew to raise pull requests (and also, scan incoming pull requests automatically for issues!)
Just like the previous AWS Github authorization, you can choose which repositories to give Bridgecrew permission to access.</description></item><item><title>Protect non CloudFormation Infrastructure</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/30_module_three/3001_bridgecrew_automate_add_runtime.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/30_module_three/3001_bridgecrew_automate_add_runtime.html</guid><description>Runtime Scanning of Vulnerable Infrastructure Last but definitley by no means least, lets answer the remaining question:
What about infrastructure that wasnt deployed by CloudFormation? Greenfield Infrastructure as Code deployments are a luxury not many of us have, with many objects in our AWS accounts often historical, created manually, or managed by a team that has not yet made the DevOps move to automation.
Scanning objects directly in the AWS environment we call &amp;ldquo;Runtime Scanning&amp;rdquo;, compared to &amp;ldquo;Build time&amp;rdquo; scanning of CloudFormation or Terraform manifests in git or as part of the CI/CD pipeline as we&amp;rsquo;ve already seen.</description></item></channel></rss>