<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on Cloud DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/5_getting_started.html</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on Cloud DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/5_getting_started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is CloudFormation?</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/5_getting_started/500_what_is_cloudformation.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/5_getting_started/500_what_is_cloudformation.html</guid><description>What is CloudFormation and Infrastructure as Code? AWS CloudFormation makes cloud provisioning simple and scalable by leveraging both automation and configuration as code. Defining your cloud infrastructure and applications as code simplifies repetitive DevOps tasks and gives you a single source of truth for app and environment configuration.
This makes it more important to make sure your infrastructure as code (IaC) resources follow security best practices—your CloudFormation configuration is now another part of your codebase, and should be tested and scanned for errors and risks just like any other code review.</description></item><item><title>Setup your Bridgecrew account</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/5_getting_started/501_setting_up_bridgecrew_account.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/5_getting_started/501_setting_up_bridgecrew_account.html</guid><description>Setup your Bridgecrew account CloudFormation gives us total control to create, change, and delete resources in AWS. With CloudFormation, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to pick and deploy any of the hundreds of templates readily available from the AWS sample templates. Because these templates are built solely with functionality in mind, it&amp;rsquo;s also easy to forget important security configuration and end up having an insecure service running in production.
That’s why scanning your CloudFormation templates before deployment is so important.</description></item><item><title>Setup git</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/5_getting_started/502_set_up_git.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/5_getting_started/502_set_up_git.html</guid><description>Check your local git installation To ensure your local git client is setup correctly, try the following commands, you should not receive an error from any of them, and end up with a copy of our &amp;lsquo;vulnerable by design&amp;rsquo; training project &amp;ldquo;CFNGoat&amp;rdquo; on your machine, which we&amp;rsquo;ll use later!
git clone https://github.com/bridgecrewio/cfngoat.git cd cfngoat git status Sample output:
$ git clone https://github.com/bridgecrewio/cfngoat.git cd cfngoat git status Cloning into &amp;#39;cfngoat&amp;#39;... remote: Enumerating objects: 64, done.</description></item></channel></rss>