<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pull requests and CI on Cloud DevSecOps workshop with Bridgecrew</title>
    <link>/kubernetes/40_pull_requests_and_ci.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pull requests and CI on Cloud DevSecOps workshop with Bridgecrew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/kubernetes/40_pull_requests_and_ci/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Bridgecrew with GitHub</title>
      <link>/kubernetes/40_pull_requests_and_ci/4001_integrate_bridgecrew_github.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kubernetes/40_pull_requests_and_ci/4001_integrate_bridgecrew_github.html</guid>
      <description>Integrate Bridgecrew with GitHub To enable automated PR scanning on your repositories, goto the **Integrations **page at the bottom of the icon bar on the left.
Then, select New Integration and select GitHub from the Code Repositories options
A pop-up dialog box will allow you to Authorize with your GitHub account and choose the repositories you want Bridgecrew to scan. Select **Authorize **to be redirected to GitHub to complete this step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create A pull request</title>
      <link>/kubernetes/40_pull_requests_and_ci/4002_create_test_pr.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kubernetes/40_pull_requests_and_ci/4002_create_test_pr.html</guid>
      <description>Create infrastructure with a pull request To see our new security controls in action, let&amp;rsquo;s create a pull request to modify our development environment configuration!
In GitHub, on your fork of KustomizeGoat, navigate into the kustomize &amp;gt; overlays and dev directories:
Select on the kustomization.yaml file to open it in the GitHub web viewer, and select edit.
Let&amp;rsquo;s make a simple change right now to trigger a build. Modify the name of the dev namespace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Block with CI</title>
      <link>/kubernetes/40_pull_requests_and_ci/4003_blocking_with_ci.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kubernetes/40_pull_requests_and_ci/4003_blocking_with_ci.html</guid>
      <description>PR scanning versus CI Our pull request annotations give good collaborative team feedback to the development teams involved, however, without extra configuration, the feedback is ecactly that, just feedback.
CI pipelines allow us to actually block (by failing) a build or change from making it from a development branch, into a main or production branch, while these two types of scans overlap, it is worth showing how you can configure Bridgecrew to sit within any CI pipeline to perform this function.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
