<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Module - Scan on Cloud DevSecOps workshop with Bridgecrew</title>
    <link>/azure/30_module_one.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Module - Scan on Cloud DevSecOps workshop with Bridgecrew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/azure/30_module_one/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TerraGoat</title>
      <link>/azure/30_module_one/1001_terragoat.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/azure/30_module_one/1001_terragoat.html</guid>
      <description>Vulnerable-by-design demo repository setup This workshop uses our vulnerable-by-design Terraform project, TerraGoat, so that you can scan and automate infrastructure code without the added friction of integrating your own code.
Fork the TerraGoat repository on GitHub To set up your demo environment, we&amp;rsquo;re going to fork the TerraGoat repository.
Head over to the TerraGoat repository and fork it using the button in the upper right corner.
If you have multiple organizations, GitHub will ask which of your orgs to fork into.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkov</title>
      <link>/azure/30_module_one/1002_local_scan_cli.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/azure/30_module_one/1002_local_scan_cli.html</guid>
      <description>If you are running Checkov with the Bridgecrew API token and you use a proxy, you may need to turn off your VPN/proxy or use the --ca-certificate flag to allow your proxy&amp;rsquo;s certificate using the directions here: https://github.com/bridgecrewio/checkov/pull/1099. If you run Checkov without the Bridgecrew API token, this won&amp;rsquo;t be an issue.
Run Checkov locally To demonstrate what kinds of security and compliance errors Bridgecrew can identify in Terraform templates, start by using Checkov and send the results to the Bridgecrew platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridgecrew Dashboard</title>
      <link>/azure/30_module_one/1003_local_scan_dashboard.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/azure/30_module_one/1003_local_scan_dashboard.html</guid>
      <description>Viewing results in Bridgecrew You just scanned your Terraform templates locally using Checkov. If you included your API key, the results were sent to the Bridgecrew platform for further investigation. You may have noticed the URL at the end of the CLI scan. That’s a direct link to the results in Bridgecrew.
Click on that link to bring up that scan’s Projects page, which is an aggregated view of the different Code Reviews across all scan types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VS Code Plugin</title>
      <link>/azure/30_module_one/1004_vs_code.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/azure/30_module_one/1004_vs_code.html</guid>
      <description>Run Checkov in your IDE You can get feedback directly in your integrated development environment (IDE) using Bridgecrew’s Checkov Visual Studio Code extension. The tool highlights misconfigurations inline and in development environments—like spell check for IaC misconfigurations.
First, you need to install the extension. In VS Code, go to Extensions and search for Checkov. Click Install.
Next, go to the Checkov Extension Settings and paste the API Token from the Bridgecrew platform that we saved earlier.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
