<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Module - Scan on Cloud DevSecOps workshop with Bridgecrew</title><link>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one.html</link><description>Recent content in Module - Scan on Cloud DevSecOps workshop with Bridgecrew</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CfnGoat</title><link>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/1001_cfngoat.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/1001_cfngoat.html</guid><description>Vulnerable-by-design demo repository setup This workshop uses our vulnerable-by-design CloudFormation project, CfnGoat, so that you can scan and automate infrastructure code without the added friction of integrating your own code. Simply clone the open-source project’s repository:
git clone https://github.com/bridgecrewio/cfngoat.git cd cfngoat git status Sample output:
$ git clone https://github.com/bridgecrewio/cfngoat.git cd cfngoat git status Cloning into &amp;#39;cfngoat&amp;#39;... remote: Enumerating objects: 64, done. remote: Counting objects: 100% (64/64), done. remote: Compressing objects: 100% (54/54), done.</description></item><item><title>Bridgecrew CLI</title><link>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/1002_local_scan_cli.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/1002_local_scan_cli.html</guid><description>Run Bridgecrew CLI locally To demonstrate what kinds of security and compliance errors Bridgecrew can identify in CloudFormation templates, we’ll start by using Bridgecrew CLI and send the results to the Bridgecrew platform.
Make sure you are in the cfngoat directory from the previous step, copy your unique Bridgecrew API token, and scan the cfngoat.yaml file:
bridgecrew -f cfngoat.yaml --bc-api-key $YOUR_BC_API_KEY --repo bridgecrewio/cfngoat You can also scan entire directories with -d &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;:</description></item><item><title>VSCode Plugin</title><link>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/1003_vscode.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/1003_vscode.html</guid><description>Visual Studio Code extension The Bridgecrew CLI can be used for a quick local scan, but is better suited when automated into a CI/CD pipeline, which we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into in Module Two.
For more developer-friendly local scanning, Bridgecrew&amp;rsquo;s Checkov VS Code extension shows scan results directly at the point of code, without having to constantly re-run the CLI tool. Results and suggested fixes are annotated directly onto the specific code block causing the violation in real-time.</description></item><item><title>Bridgecrew Dashboard</title><link>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/1004_local_scan_dashboard.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://workshop.bridgecrew.io/aws/10_module_one/1004_local_scan_dashboard.html</guid><description>Viewing results in Bridgecrew In the previous section, we scanned our demo CloudFormation repository locally with both standalone CLI and the Checkob VSCode plugin, and sent the results to the Bridgecrew platform for investigation and remediation.
To explore the reported issues we saw in the CLI output, head to the Incidents tab in your Bridgecrew account.
Bridgecrew comes with hundreds of out-of-the-box policies to help you adhere to cloud security best practices as defined by the Center of Internet Security (CIS).</description></item></channel></rss>