<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>One | Finding CloudFormation misconfigurations locally on Cloud DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/10_module_one.html</link><description>Recent content in One | Finding CloudFormation misconfigurations locally on Cloud DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/10_module_one/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your Bridgecrew API Key</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/10_module_one/1001_bridgecrew_api_key.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/10_module_one/1001_bridgecrew_api_key.html</guid><description>Your Bridgecrew API Key To run the Bridgecrew CLI we installed with pip3 earlier, you’ll need an API token from your bridgecrew account.
To get it, go here! (https://www.bridgecrew.cloud/integrations/api-token) or, when logged into the bridgecrew console, go to Integrations &amp;gt; API Token and copy the token provided!</description></item><item><title>Bridgecrew CLI</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/10_module_one/1002_local_scan_cli.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/10_module_one/1002_local_scan_cli.html</guid><description>Scan a repo locally with the bridgecrew CLI We use the Bridgecrew API token to connect our local Bridgecrew CLI with the Bridgecrew cloud, the following command will scan the CFNGoat repository we cloned for infrastructure vulnerabilitues and display any issues and violations.
The API key also sends these results to the Bridgecrew cloud for so we can track, inspect in more detail and remediate them there, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover this a little later.</description></item><item><title>Bridgecrew Dashboard</title><link>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/10_module_one/1003_local_scan_dashboard.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aws-modernization-workshop-bridgecrew/10_module_one/1003_local_scan_dashboard.html</guid><description>Viewing our results in the Bridgecrew Dashboard If we access the Bridgecrew dashboard at https://bridgecrew.cloud we will see statistics for the configuration issues and policy violations found by the Bridgecrew CLI in our cfngoat repository, feel free to explore the dashboard, then click onto the &amp;ldquo;Incidents&amp;rdquo; tab on the left navigation bar to drill down and explore the reported issues we saw on the CLI output in more details.</description></item></channel></rss>